<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sairas ko website</title>
    <link>https://sairas.tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sairas ko website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 12:26:17 +0545</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sairas.tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Php Wrappers</title>
      <link>https://sairas.tech/posts/php-wrappers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 12:26:17 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sairas.tech/posts/php-wrappers/</guid>
      
      <description>PHP Wrappers and Remote Code Execution (RCE) In the context of Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerabilities, PHP wrappers play a crucial role in how external resources or data are handled by PHP scripts. Wrappers essentially allow PHP to access various data sources, including files, URLs, and even remote systems. When misconfigured, PHP wrappers can facilitate an attacker’s ability to execute arbitrary commands, leading to potential RCE vulnerabilities. Below, I’ll cover some important PHP wrappers and how they can be exploited, with a specific focus on the role of allow_url_include, input, and data wrappers.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annie Ctf</title>
      <link>https://sairas.tech/posts/annie-ctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 01:45:35 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sairas.tech/posts/annie-ctf/</guid>
      
      <description>This lab was relativey simple but taught me a lot of things
Enumeration The thing I like to do is find all the open ports with rustscan and then run nmap for futher analysis, it makes my thing faster by about 10 minutes. So I ran these following commands
rustscan -a $ip -b 65535 -u 5000 | tee rustscan Then I run nmap on the found ports
sudo nmap $ip -p xxx,xxx -sV -sC I saw that two ports were open, One was ssh on 22 and real server on 7070</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://sairas.tech/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sairas.tech/about/</guid>
      
      <description>About Me Hello you, welcome to my Website. I&amp;rsquo;m Sairas, a penetration tester &amp;amp; an active member of NCA@Nepal. This is where I share my thoughts, experiences, and projects.
Feel free to explore my posts and reach out if you&amp;rsquo;d like to connect!
Intrested in: Web Application Security Penetration Testing Python Programming Rust Programming Reverse Engineering/PWN Assembly Language </description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
